http://www.natalieanddonnell.com/privacy-policy/

0
was successfully added to your cart.No menu assigned! PrivacyNatalie and Donnell know that your privacy is important to you and they have created this policy to explain what personal information is gathered when you visit this website and how that information is used. By using this website, you signify your agreement to this policy.When you visit our website, we do automatically collect any personal information, although some non-personal information, such as your browser, operating systems and IP address may be automatically collected.You may be invited to submit personal information such as name, mailing address or email address when you sign up for our newsletter.  This information is used for marketing and promotional purposes by Natalie and Donnell but is not shared with third parties.  By providing the personal information to us, you agree and consent to the collection, use and/or disclosure of such information by for the purposes stated above.We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 16 and if you are under 16, please do not register for any services using this site or send us any personal information.Although no data transmission over the internet can be 100% secure, we do employ security measures to protect your data.Use of Cookies And Other TechnologiesCookies are pieces of information that a web site transfers to an individual’s computer hard drive for record keeping purposes. Cookies make using the Site easier by, among other things, saving your passwords and preferences for you. For example, we use cookies to keep track of your shopping cart when you visit our online store, and help identify you when you return to the store. These cookies are restricted for use only on the site, and do not transfer any personal information to any other party. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies; however, you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. (Note: you will need to consult the help area of your browser application for instructions.) If you choose to disable your cookies setting or refuse to accept a cookie, some parts of the site may not function properly or may be considerably slower. We may link to websites that are operated by third parties and if you choose to visit those websites, you should refer to each site’s respective privacy policy as our privacy policy only governs our site.If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, contact us at lgelfand@lauriegelfand.com    Get In the Know EMAIL ADDRESS*
POSTAL/ZIP CODE* By submitting this form, you agree to the Natalie MacMaster & Donnell Leahy Privacy Policy.
Natalie MacMaster & Donnell Leahy: A Celtic Family Christmas
$15.00© 2020 MACMASTER MUSIC INC. | Privacy Policy | WEBSITE DESIGN : THE LAUNDRY DESIGN WORKSHomeA Celtic Family ChristmasGreenbridge Celtic Folk FestivalNatalie MacMasterDonnell LeahyNatalie, Donnell & FamilyMacMaster Leahy KidsShowsMusicNewsGalleryHeritageRecipesShopPromotersContact
